https://www.soundbroker.com/about/#privacy

Twitter Feed
Tweets by @soundbroker
702.736.3003
(0)
ADC
ADJ (American DJ)
ALLISON RESEARCH
ALPS ELECTRIC CO. LTD.
BRAINSTORM
BRAINSTORM, FASTFORWARD, COMREX,GENTNER,
CENTREX
CENTURY IND.
DIGICO
DIGIDESIGN (AVID)
EAR
EARPEACE TECHNOLOGIES, INC.
EARTHWORKS
EAW (Eastern Acoustics Works)
EUROLITE
EV (ELECTROVOICE)
EXTRON
F.A.L.
FX
GAE (GERMANAUDIOENGINEERING)
INDUSTRIAL ACOUSTIC SOLUTIONS
INDUSTRIAL ACOUSTICS CO. INC.
OXMOOR
P&L (POWER & LIGHT PRODUCTIONS)
SURGEX
SVS INC.
TRUE / NEUMANN
TRUE VISION, INC. (TVI)
UNIVERSAL AUDIO
UNIVERSAL MFG.
About the Company & Owner, Jan Landy
(Celebrating our 23rd anniversary linking buyers and sellers)
Thank you for visiting SoundBroker.com - a membership based sales organization linking buyers and sellers together since 1997. We are THE marketplace for the buying and selling of professional audio, lighting, staging and video equipment. The SoundBroker.com website contains over 85,173 new and pre-owned equipment listings worth more than $100 million and is updated on a real time basis. Our specialty is liquidating manufacturers' discontinued and pre-owned inventory from pro sound and lighting companies and recording studios.
If this is your first time visiting SoundBroker.com , you can expect high levels of customer service, logistical support, and a process which boasts an integrity that's been documented over the years. Our pledge is to always provide truthful answers to your questions in a timely manner, fair and competitive pricing, and a Guarantee of Satisfaction on every transaction. We offer you the best prices and an enormous inventory to choose from. SoundBroker.com prides itself on being the best place on earth to buy and sell professional entertainment production equipment.
For those of you who assisted in getting us to where we are today, I appreciate your loyalty and your trust. Over 60% of our business is from YOU, our current member base. We are constantly looking for new ways to make your shopping experience more pleasurable and efficient.
All my best,
Jan Landy - CEO, Founder
SoundBroker.com
Notice:
PRICING POLICY WE DO NOT SET THE PRICES. All listing prices are set by the seller and include our fees. Due to the large number of listings we receive, we do not verify whether or not the asking price is fair market value. It is our belief that the buyer is the best judge of what their needs are and how much they should pay. Therefore, it is the responsibility of the buyer to determine value. Please note our statement on every page of our web site: "Contact us to make a fair counteroffer if a listing is priced too high!!!".
Unfortunately, there is a limited amount of price flexibility on listings under $2,500.00. Any taxes, shipping, and handling are paid for by the buyer. It is our responsibility to protect both the buyer and the seller, and we guarantee that you get what you pay for.
PRIVACY STATEMENT SoundBroker.com keeps your personal information private and secure. In order to most efficiently serve you, fulfillment of all Gold Member orders are taken off-site by telephone, fax, or email. To keep you informed about our latest offers, we may notify you of current promotions, specials, and/or new additions to our site.
Our History SoundBroker started in the summer of 1997 when Jan was hired by Disneyfest Asia to market and sell a huge warehouse full of equipment. All of this equipment was either brand new or slightly used. Working under a deadline of only 5 weeks, he had to move quickly, and he did. At the end of the 5-week period, Jan had sold everything from the storage area.
Having successfully completed this project, he realized that there were many other individuals and organizations that had the same need. This thought led to the birth of Soundbroker.com : A firm dedicated to "Sales Brokering" and liquidation of technical equipment inventories. Jan's next client was JBL Professional, who contracted him to sell their discontinued and B-Stock inventory. And the rest, as they say, is history.
SoundBroker.com is now the world's number one site of its kind and has more sound and lighting equipment listed than any other site in the entire world including eBay.
Welcome to SoundBroker.com's Privacy Statement Page.
For years, our policy statement was one paragraph and not one member's information was ever jeopardized in any way, shape, or form. It read:
SoundBroker.com keeps your personal information private and secure. In order to most efficiently serve you, fulfillment of all Gold Member orders are taken off-site by telephone, fax or email. To keep you informed about our latest offers, we may notify you of current promotions, specials and new additions to our site.
SoundBroker.com continues to provide the highest level of website security to keep your information safe. Today with all the new laws and policy changes, the following further explains the above in clearer terms:
What information do we collect?
SoundBroker.com collects information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, or credit card information. If preferred, however, you may visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: a) To personalize your experience as your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs b) To improve our website as we continually strive to improve our offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you c)To improve customer service as your information helps us to more effectively respond to your service requests and support needs
To process transactions, your information whether public or private will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever without your consent other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To send periodic emails, the email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product/service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your any of your personal information, and when you place an order. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment Gateway provider's database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems who are required to keep the information confidential.
During a transaction, you can securely save your credit card and/or checking account information with your account to enable future purchases to be completed faster.
Your information is stored according to PCI Compliance standards.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser if your personal settings allow. Cookies enable the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser, capture, and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent. Or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you so long as said parties agree to keep all information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our own or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links: Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of SoundBroker.com and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act); we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years of age or older.
Terms and Conditions: Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.SoundBroker.com
Your Consent: By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy: If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us: If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
© Copyright 1997 - 2020 SoundBroker.com. All Rights Reserved.
